IMPORTANT NOTES 
--Please read the following 


The purpose of this thesis project was to investigate the security issues that might occur in information systems, if multiple users own the same applications. Cyberdiversity as a term is based on biology and specifically in biodiversity. Cyberdiverse computer systems could prove to be more resistant to potential attacks than systems that tend to monoculture. Monocultures can be characterized as a population that consists of identical members that belong to the same type. In a monoculture, when a piece of malware manage to contaminate one member of the system, it can affect the rest of it due to the fat that they all share the same vulnerabilities.The reason for me choosing the theme “Cyberdiversity in Information Systems” was the need to examine if the phenomenon of monoculture exists in information systems and in what exend in software that we use today. 
This thesis is supervised by  Dr. Vasileios Vlachos

We do not keep track on any of our users' activity such as any type of documents, files and Internet activity. 


In order to run this application, follow the instructions below:
 

1.The computer that is examined should have Windows software and Java Software. It runs for every Java edition 
2. If you don't hava the Java installed, please download from here : https://java.com/en/download/ 
3. In the file pc_client, there is a .bat file called thesis.bat, it is clickable and you should only click on the file and the application woul start running automatically. 


Thank you in advance for your help,
Zacharouli Markella 

